Alfredo Quezada

Personal info

Phone:

(858) 337-5718

Email:

aquezadat@hotmail.com

Skills

Java



HTML, CSS, and Python



Matlab programming language



C++



English and Spanish



German



Chinese Mandarin



Office Word, Powerpoint, Excel



Lab research



Mathematics



Professional Summary

Experienced Research Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the research industry. Skilled in Programming, Mathematics, Applied Physics, and Biology. Strong research 3rd year Undergraduate focused in Marine Biology at Scripps Institution of Oceanography from the University of California, San Diego.

Employment history

Research Assistant, UCSD Eating Disorders Research and Treatment Center. La Jolla, California

Jan. 2017 - Present

Work between 6 and 8 hours a week. Help by analyzing data, helping in logistics, and/or providing assistance during research procedures. All of this is done within the neurosciences and brain imaging department of the Research center.

Logistics and Accounting Assistant, Comenzar de Nuevo A.C.. Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico

Jun. 2016 - Aug. 2018

Worked as an intern during the summers for an average of 40 hours per week. Provided assistance by organizing patients' files, designing a program to store all files, and helping create a more efficient working environment.

Education

University of California, San Diego, La Jolla, California Bachelor of Science, Marine Biology, Present

Preparatoria Tecnológico de Monterrey de Estudios Superiores Campus Santa Catarina, Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico

High School Diploma, Jun. 2016

International Experience

Intensive german course during summer of 2015 with the school Heidelberg Pädagogium (2 months).

Community Service

Volunteer at several orphanages and shelters during the years 2013 - 2015. 3 hours a week on Saturdays (over 60 hours in total), 7 weeks per semester. This include: Casa Hogar Douglas, Asilo Virgen de Guadalupe, and Casa Hogar para Ancianitos María Esperanza Nuestra.

Additional information

Has taken part in 7 student groups from High School to college:

FELC 2014/Competitor

FELC is a congress dedicated to business management. Competitors compete
between them to create a business and dedicate themselves to make it thrive in the
high school environment.

Hackathon 2014/Competitor Hackathon 2015/Competitor

 Hackathon is a congress dedicated to encourage programming between students of high schools around our city. Competitors have 24 hours inside the high school's installations to create a software and present it with the purpose of winning one of the first three places.

Challenge Accepted 2015/Board, Secretary

 Challenge Accepted is a congress dedicated to encourage the artistic diversity between students, leadership, and teamwork.

Resorte 2015/Board, Treasurer

• Resorte is a congress which looks to encourage social responsibility by showing current problems of our country through the arts.

Faith 2015/Staff

• Faith is a student group dedicated to organize events with the purpose of raising funds in order to help a child with cancer to pay his/her medical needs.

Further 2015/Staff

• Further is a student group that encourages education, the staff is made up of tutors which help students in need to prepare for exams or just help them understand certain topics with which they struggle with.